Finding Aid for the Pinal Dome Oil Company Records LSC.0220
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Legal Documents
  - 1917 (Box 90)
  - Including abstracts of title., 1894-1906 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Including articles of incorporation, by-laws, and indentures of Pinal Oil Company., 1901-1903 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Including indentures and Dome Oil articles of incorporation., 1904-1906 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Including articles of incorporation and by-laws of Santa Maria Oil and Transportation Company and by-laws of Vesper Mining Company., 1907-1910 (Box 95)
  - 1917-1918 (Box 97)
  - 1912-1915 (Box 98)
  - 1910-1920 (Box 99)
  - Vesper Mining Company by-laws and organization., 1910 (Box 102)
  - 1901-1910 (Box 108)
  - 1900-1913 (Box 109)
  - 1902-1904 (Box 110)
  - 1896-1913 (Box 111)
  - 1893-1911 (Box 112)
  - 1902-1914 (Box 113)
  - 1901-1916 (Box 114)
  - Claims to trademark., 1907-1913; [oversized] (Box 116)